# **Nguyen Khac Ngoc Khoi**

# Front-End Developer

0384111265 • khoi.nkn12@gmail.com • https://nknk-vn.github.io/portfolio • Ho Chi Minh City

#### **Summary**

I am an experienced front-end developer with two years of industry experience, demonstrating the ability to create intuitive user interfaces. Familiar with front-end development concepts, I am a goal-driven individual seeking opportunities to work in a professional environment and expand my knowledge and skills. I aspire to transition into a full-stack developer role.

#### **Education**

### **VNUHCM - University of Information Technology (UIT)**

**Computer Engineering** 

Ho Chi Minh City Sep 2015 - Jun 2021

### **Experience**

**PROTONX** Ha Noi

**Front-End Developer** 

Sep 2022 - Apr 2024

Developed an education website to help users create and manage their content and students more efficiently. This website utilizes the MERN stack:

- Designed and improved the user interface for a website that allows teachers to create and manage classes and necessary teaching materials.
- Developed a user-friendly interface for students with features that support the learning process.
- Implemented automated email tools and integrated AI for content creation.
- Designed APIs for CRUD tasks using Express.js and MongoDB.
- Developed an advertising website for courses using Next.js, optimizing it for SEO.
- Deployed the website on Cloudflare.

Technologies used: React.js, Bootstrap, Redux, Next.js, Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB.

#### THE UNIVERSITY OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

## **Research Assistant**

Ho Chi Minh City Jun 2019 - Mar 2021

Sensitive object detection:

- Researched basic and modern neural network architectures and their application.
- Evaluated the performance of object detection models on custom datasets.
- Working on object detection using model YOLO.
- Apply model text and object detection on Chrome Extension.

Technologies used: Python, Tensorflow, YOLO.

#### **Skills**

Frontend: HTML, CSS, React.js, Next.js Backend: Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB

Tools: Git, Docker, Linux

## **Publications**

LSPD: A Large-Scale Pornographic Dataset for Detection and Classification Duy Phan, Thien Nguyen, Huy Nguyen, Loc Tran, <b>Khoi Nguyen</b> and Lung Vu	IJIES, 2021
A Novel Pornographic Visual Content Classifier based on Sensitive Object Detection Duy Phan, Thien Nguyen, Huy Nguyen, Loc Tran, <b>Khoi Nguyen</b> and Lung Vu	IJACSA, 2021
Khảo sát bài toán nhận diện phương tiện và đo tốc độ phương tiện tham gia giao thôn Loc Tran, <b>Khoi Nguyen</b> , Duy Phan, Lung Vu	g FAIR, 2020
Additional learning on object detection: a novel approach in pornography classification Loc Tran, Huy Nguyen, Duy Phan, Thien Nguyen, <b>Khoi Nguyen</b> and Lung Vu	<u>FDSE</u> , 2020
Multi-level detector for pornographic content using CNN models Huy Nguyen, Khoi Nguyen, Loc Tran, Thien Nguyen, Duy Phan and Lung Vu	RIVF International Conference, 2020

## Certification

Structuring Machine Learning Projects - Coursera	Oct 2021
Improving Deep Neural Networks: Hyperparameter Tuning, Regularization and Optimization - Coursera	Sep 2021
Neural Networks and Deep Learning - Coursera	Sep 2021
Tensorflow Developer Certificate - Tensorflow	Aug 2021 - Aug 2024
Toeic 510 - ETS IIG Vietnam	Aug 2020 - Aug 2022